<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IMCS</string>
    <string name="CURVA_CC">Constant Curve</string>
    <string name="btn_help">HELP</string>
    <string name="NOTE_esempio">Preloaded Example Data: Mixed 520 cm mast with Gastra Bottom and Amex Top</string>
    <string name="CURVA_CCFT">Constant Curve - Flex Top</string>
    <string name="CURVA_FT">Flex Top</string>
    <string name="CURVA_FTSFT">Flex Top - Super Flex Top</string>
    <string name="CURVA_HT">Hard Top</string>
    <string name="CURVA_HTCC">Hard Top - Constant Curve</string>
    <string name="CURVA_SFT">Super Flex Top</string>
    <string name="TV_CURVA">CURVE</string>
    <string name="TV_FLEX">FLEX</string>
    <string name="TV_IMCS">IMCS</string>
    <string name="TV_h01">High &#188; L [mm]</string>
    <string name="TV_h02">High &#189; L [mm]:</string>
    <string name="TV_h03">High &#190; L [mm]:</string>
    <string name="TV_hb">High at Bottom [mm]:</string>
    <string name="TV_ht">High at Top [mm]:</string>
    <string name="TV_prjinfo">Data Test</string>
    <string name="TV_risultati">RESULTS</string>
    <string name="Titolo_graph">Mast Bend Curve</string>
    <string name="btn_risultati">RESULTS</string>
    <string name="d1">Diameter &#188; L [mm]:</string>
    <string name="d2">Diameter &#189; L [mm]:</string>
    <string name="d3">Diameter &#190; L [mm]:</string>
    <string name="db">Bottom Diameter [mm]:</string>
    <string name="dt">Top Diameter [mm]:</string>
    <string name="misure">DEFLECTIONS</string>
    <string name="misure_c">Loaded Mast</string>
    <string name="misure_s">Pre-Bend Sag</string>
    <string name="title_activity_geometry">Mast Geometry</string>
    <string name="txt_back">Back</string>
    <string name="txt_btn_Nuovo">New</string>
    <string name="txt_btn_Vecchio">Fetch Existent</string>
    <string name="txt_btn_imm">Forward</string>
    <string name="txt_calcola">Calculate</string>
    <string name="txt_edit_idAlbero">Mast Id</string>
    <string name="txt_edit_marcaAlbero">Mast Brand</string>
    <string name="txt_ln">Length [cm]:</string>
    <string name="txt_mledit_note">Note</string>
    <string name="txt_view_Geometria">Mast Dimensions</string>
    <string name="txt_view_idAlbero">Mast Id</string>
    <string name="txt_view_marcaAlbero">Mast Brand</string>
    <string name="txt_view_note">Note</string>
    <string name="help_title">IMCS EVALUATION AND MEASURES</string>
      <string name="Mess_Help_00">
        <b>PROCEDURE</b>\n
        In order to perform all the measurements necessary to workout the IMCS and Flex values, the
          following steps have to be carried out:\n
          1) set up the mast;\n
          2) measure the mast length [cm];\n
          3) put some adesive tape around it at 5 points: top, bottom, half and the two
          quarters of the mast length near the mast top and the bottom;\n
          4) measure the diameters [mm] at the points where the tape has been positioned;\n
          5) lay the mast placing  the mast top and bottom on two supports;\n
          6) measure the distance from the top diameter of the mast to the level ground [cm] in the five
          points where the pieces of tape are placed;\n
          7) load the mast in its middle with 30kg;\n
          8) repeat the instructions at point 6);\n
          9) fill in the specific application text fields with the data collected.
    </string>
   <string name="Mess_Help_001">
    <b>Useful Info</b>\n
        <i>(Source Unifiber and Tushingham)</i>\n
    The key points you have to take into account when choosing a mast are:\n
    1. Flex \n
    2. Stiffnes (IMCS) \n
    3. Carbon fiber percentage \n
    </string>
    <string name="Mess_Help_01">
        <b>Curvature (Flex)\n</b>
Curvature, aka FLEX, represents the bent shape of the mast when loaded by the rigged sail. Normally the cross sections
        of the typical mast decrease starting from the bottom tapering toward the top. The larger
        cross sections at the bottom determine higher stiffness and, as a consequence, less bending
        of the lower part of the mast with respect to the upper part of it. The FLEX parameter
        represents the amount of difference between the deformation of the upper part and
        that of the lower part of a mast. The industry standard terms describing windsurfing mast
        bend curves are:\n
<i>0-6 = Hard top\n
7-9 = Hard Top/Constant Curve\n
10-12 = Constant Curve\n
13-15 =Constant Curve/Flex top\n
16-18 = Flex Top\n
19-21 = Flex Top/Super Flex Top\n
22+ = Super Flex Top</i>\n
        The higher the number the more flexible the mast is in the upper half relative to the bottom.
        The Flex Top masts, more flexible near the top, are build following different criteria with
        respect to the Hard Top, stiffer near the top.\n
FLEX is calculated as a percentage ratio between:\n
        - the difference between the deformations taken respectively at 1/4 of L from the TOP and the Bottom;\n
        - the deformation of the mast in its middle;\n
        when the mast is loaded with a weight of 30Kg in its middle.
    </string>
    <string name="Mess_Help_02">
        <b>Stiffness (IMCS)</b>\n

        Stiffness, commonly referred to as IMCS (Indexed Mast Check System), is an indication of how much
        a mast bends when it is loaded.
        Normally the IMCS varies from 6 to 38. The higher the IMCS the stiffer the mast. Most of the mast brands
        usually adopt standard values of IMCS with reference to standard lengths. For instance often 400cm masts
        have IMCS 19, whereas 430cm masts have IMCS 21 and 490cm masts have IMCS 29. It is easy to
        realize that these different masts of different lengths, have all a tipical MCS of 25 (which
        in turn shows that almost any mast has the same deformation in the middle).\n

        The numerical value of the IMCS results from the ratio between:
        - the length of the mast raised to the power of three;
        - the product of 460 (or 465) squared and the deformation in the middle
        when the mast is loaded with a weight of 30kh in its middle.
    </string>
    <string name="Mess_Help_03"><b>Carbon percentage content</b>\n
        The content of carbon fiber (with respect to the concomitant content of different kinds of other
        fibers such as glass) varies usually between 30 and 100. The higher the content of carbon fiber, the
        more reactive and lighter the rig will be which, in turn, will result in a better control.
        As a result, the sails performances will improve when masts with high carbon percentage are used.
    </string>
    <string name="TV_Lref">IMCS Reference Length [cm]</string>
</resources>